[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797bef4dccfa540cc608020"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "What is React ?",
  "options": [
    "Bundler",
    "Framework",
    "Library",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Library"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c4fe264bc797e7bf06da"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following are the advantages of React.js?",
  "options": [
    "React.js can increase the application's performance with Virtual DOM.",
    "React.js is easy to integrate with other frameworks such as Angular, BackboneJS since it is only a view library.",
    "React.js can render both on client and server side.",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c56f264bc797e7bf06dc"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is not a disadvantage of React.js?",
  "options": [
    "React.js has only a view layer. We have put your code for Ajax requests, events and so on.",
    "The library of React.js is pretty large.",
    "The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
    "The learning curve can be steep in React.js."
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c5fe264bc797e7bf06de"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
  "options": [
    "Original DOM",
    "Virtual DOM",
    "All of the above",
    "None of the above."
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Virtual DOM",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c63b264bc797e7bf06e0"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "A class is a type of function, but instead of using the keyword function to initiate it, which keyword do we use?",
  "options": [
    "Constructor",
    "Class",
    "Object",
    "DataObject"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Class",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c667264bc797e7bf06e2"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following acts as the input of a class-based component?",
  "options": [
    "Class",
    "Factory",
    "Render",
    "Props"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Props",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c69b264bc797e7bf06e4"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following keyword is used to create a class inheritance?",
  "options": [
    "Create",
    "Inherits",
    "Extends",
    "This"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Extends",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c6e9264bc797e7bf06e6"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "What is the default port where webpack-server runs?",
  "options": [
    "3000",
    "8080",
    "3030",
    "6060"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "8080",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c702264bc797e7bf06e8"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "How many numbers of elements a valid react component can return?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "1",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c73b264bc797e7bf06ea"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "What is the declarative way to render a dynamic list of components based on values in an array?",
  "options": [
    "Using the reduce array method",
    "Using the <Each /> component",
    "Using the Array.map() method",
    "With a for/while loop"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Using the Array.map() method",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c76c264bc797e7bf06ec"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": " How many ways of defining your variables in ES6?",
  "options": [
    "1",
    "3",
    "5",
    "4"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "3",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c7a9264bc797e7bf06ee"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "What is a state in React?",
  "options": [
    "A permanent storage.",
    "Internal storage of the component.",
    "External storage of the component.",
    "None of the above."
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Internal storage of the component.",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c805264bc797e7bf06f0"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "What are the two ways to handle data in React?",
  "options": [
    "State & Props",
    "Services & Components",
    "State & Services",
    "State & Component"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "State & Props.",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c85c264bc797e7bf06f2"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following option is correct in the case of the Babel?",
  "options": [
    "Babel is a Compiler.",
    "Babel is a Transpilar",
    "None of the above.",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "All of the above.",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6797c8af264bc797e7bf06f4"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135c7"
  },
  "question": " What does ES6 stand for?",
  "options": [
    "ECMAScript 6",
    "ECMA 6",
    "ECMAJavaScript 6",
    "EJavaScript 6"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "ECMAScript 6",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798a97d264bc797e7bf06f6"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Who is credited as the developer of Express.js?",
  "options": [
    "Larry wall",
    "Rich Hickey",
    "TJ Holowaychuk",
    "Rob Pike"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "TJ Holowaychuk",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798a9b9264bc797e7bf06f8"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "What is the way to store local variables that can be accessed within the application?",
  "options": [
    "Using Config file",
    "Using database",
    "Using app.locals",
    "Using app.storage"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Using app.locals",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798a9fa264bc797e7bf06fa"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "In combination with a request method, root paths define the endpoints at which requests can be made. Which of the following are valid forms of route path?",
  "options": [
    "strings",
    "string patterns",
    "regular expressions",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798aa39264bc797e7bf06fc"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Where are the captured values populated regarding the route parameters?",
  "options": [
    "req.data",
    "app.locals",
    "req.params",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "req.params",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798aa70264bc797e7bf06fe"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following function arguments are available to Express.js Route handlers?",
  "options": [
    "req - the request object",
    "res - the response object",
    "next",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798abb0264bc797e7bf0700"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is a middleware in Express.js?",
  "options": [
    "function(req){ }",
    "method(req){ }",
    "function(req,res,next){ }",
    "method(req,res,next){ }"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "function(req,res,next){ }",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798abf8264bc797e7bf0702"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is the correct statement in the context of Express.js?",
  "options": [
    "Express is a minimal and flexible Node.js web application framework.",
    "Express is a minimal and flexible React.js web application framework.",
    "Express is a minimal and flexible Redux.js web application framework.",
    "Express is a minimal and flexible Angular.js web application framework."
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Express is a minimal and flexible Node.js web application framework.",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798ae73264bc797e7bf0704"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to use Express.js in Node?",
  "options": [
    "var = require('express')();",
    "var_require('express')();",
    "var app = require('express')();",
    "None of the above."
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "var app = require('express')();",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798aeaa264bc797e7bf0706"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "To use Mongo with Express.js, we need a client API for node.",
  "options": [
    "TRUE",
    "FALSE",
    "Can be true or false",
    "Cannot say"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798aed4264bc797e7bf0708"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following facilitates us to create a skeleton for a web application easily?",
  "options": [
    "Authentication",
    "APIs",
    "Debugging",
    "Scaffolding"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Scaffolding",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798af0f264bc797e7bf070a"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is a middleware that parses cookies attached to the client request object?",
  "options": [
    "cookie",
    "cookies",
    "cookie-parser",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "cookie-parser",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798af41264bc797e7bf070c"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "The method of using values is called?",
  "options": [
    "filters",
    "interpolation",
    "inheritance",
    "includes"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "interpolation",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798af7e264bc797e7bf070e"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following command is used to check the current version of NPM?",
  "options": [
    "nmp --ver",
    "npm --version",
    "npm help",
    "None"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "npm --version",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798afac264bc797e7bf0710"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following method requests that the server accept the data enclosed in the request to modify an existing object identified by the URI?",
  "options": [
    "GET",
    "DELETE",
    "PUT",
    "POST"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "PUT",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b3f1264bc797e7bf0712"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135bb"
  },
  "question": "HTTP is stateless.",
  "options": [
    "This statement is true.",
    "This statement is false.",
    "It can be true or false.",
    "Cannot say."
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "This statement is true.",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b481264bc797e7bf0714"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which one of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",
  "options": [
    ".py",
    ".python",
    ".p",
    "None"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": ".py",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b4a5264bc797e7bf0716"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "What do we use to define a block of code in Python language?",
  "options": [
    "Key",
    "Brackets",
    "Indentation",
    "None"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Indentation",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b4cc264bc797e7bf0718"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which character is used in Python to make a single line comment?",
  "options": [
    "/",
    "//",
    "#",
    "!"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "#",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b505264bc797e7bf071a"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "What is the method inside the class in python language?",
  "options": [
    "Object",
    "Function",
    "Attribute",
    "Argument"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Function",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b52e264bc797e7bf071c"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following is not a keyword in Python language?",
  "options": [
    "val",
    "raise",
    "try",
    "with"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "val",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b55e264bc797e7bf071e"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following words cannot be a variable in python language?",
  "options": [
    "_val",
    "val",
    "try",
    "_try_"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "try",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b58c264bc797e7bf0720"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following operators is the correct option for power(ab)?",
  "options": [
    "a ^ b",
    "a**b",
    "a ^ ^ b",
    "a ^ * b"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "a**b",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b7de264bc797e7bf0722"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which one of the following has the highest precedence in the expression?",
  "options": [
    "Division",
    "Subtraction",
    "Power",
    "Parentheses"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Parentheses",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798b95e264bc797e7bf0724"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "round(4.576) What will be the output of this function?",
  "options": [
    "4",
    "5",
    "576",
    "6"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "5",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798bb4d264bc797e7bf0726"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "Which of the following option is not a core data type in the python language?",
  "options": [
    "Dictionary",
    "Lists",
    "Class",
    "All"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Class",
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6798bbc8264bc797e7bf0728"
  },
  "courseId": {
    "$oid": "66fba9fefd644d47f4f135be"
  },
  "question": "What happens when '2' == 2 is executed?",
  "options": [
    "False",
    "True",
    "ValueError occurs",
    "TypeError occurs"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "False",
  "__v": 0
}]